Finding Aid for the Ronald Jacobs Papers PASC.0355
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Dick Van Dyke Show (The)
  - Where Did I Come From? - script, 1961 Sep 27 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Who and Where was Wally Woolworth - revised script, 1963 Sep 6 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Who Stole My Watch - script, 1965 Aug 19 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - You Ought to be in Pictures - script, 1966 Feb 22 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    Writers: Winter, Jack
  - Young Man With a Shoehorn - script, 1964 Nov 13 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Writers: Belson; Marshall
  - Your Home Sweet Home is My Home - script, 1964 Jan 14 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - You're Under Arrest - script, 1965 Jul 30 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Writers: Cavella, Joseph C.
- Gomer Pyle USMC
  - Arrivederci, Gomer - revised script, 1965 Nov 12 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Writers: Bullock, Harvey; Allen, R. S.
  - Borrowed Car (The) - script, 1966 Jun 20 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Captain Ironpants - revised script, 1964 Jun 22 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Care of the Marine Bandit (The) - revised script, 1964 Aug 26 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Cat Overboard - revised script, 1965 Aug 23 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Caution: Low Overhead - revised script, 1966 Jun 30 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Writers: Brenner, Ray; Blitzer, Barry E.
  - Cold Nose, Warm heart - revised script, 1966 Aug 24 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Crazy Legs Gomer - revised script, 1966 Jun 22 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Crow Ganef (The) - revised script, 1967 Jan 26 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Dance, Marine, Dance - revised script, 1964 Sep 23 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Date for the Colonel's Daughter (A) - revised script, 1964 Aug 10 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Date with Miss Camp Henderson (A) - revised script, 1966 Feb 7 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Writers: Kleinschmitt; McRaven
  - Daughter of the Sarge - script, 1964 Nov 10 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Writers: Bullock, Harvey; Allen, R.S.
  - Desk Job for Sergeant Carter - revised script, 1966 Mar 7 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Double Date with the Sarge - revised script, 1965 Jan 11 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Writers: Powell, Richard M.
  - Duke Slater, Night Club Comic - revised script, 1966 Jan 24 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Fending Pyles (The) - revised script, 1964 Oct 5 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Writers: Kraft, Hy
  - Follow that Car - revised script, 1966 Sep 22 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Writers: Blitzer, Barry E.; Brenner, Ray
  - Go Blow Your Horn - revised script, 1966 Oct 21 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Gomer and the Beast - revised script, 1965 Nov 29 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Gomer and the Card Shark - script, 1966 Oct 28 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Gomer and the Dragon Lady - revised script, 1964 Jul 27 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Gomer and the Father Figure - revised script, 1966 Feb 9 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Gomer and the Little Men from Outer Space - revised script, 1966 Jul 21 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Gomer and the Phone company - revised script, 1966 Jan 3 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Gomer Captures a Submarine - revised script, 1965 Aug 24 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Gomer Dates a Movie Star - revised script, 1965 Jan 28 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Writers: Grossman, Budd
  - Gomer Learns a Bully - script, 1964 Jun 16 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Gomer Makes the Honor Guard, 1964 Dec 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Gomer Minds the Sergeant's Car - revised script, 1965 Oct 11 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Gomer overcomes the Obstacle Course - script, 1964 Apr 21 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Gomer Pyle, Civilian - revised script, 1965 Nov 8 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Gomer Pyle, P.O.W. - revised script, 1965 Nov 12 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Gomer Pyle, Super Chef - revised script, 1966 Aug 10 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Gomer the MP - revised script, 1965 Feb 4 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Gomer Un-Trains a Dog - revised script, 1965 Jul 6 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Gomer, the Carrier - revised script, 1966 Jul 7 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Gomer, the Peacemaker - revised script, 1965 Oct 21 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Gomer, the Recruiter - revised script, 1966 Oct 6 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Gomer, the Star Witness - script, 1965 Sep 20 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Gomer, the Welsh Rarebit Fiend - script, 1966 Dec 1966 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Gomer, the Wild Savage beast - script, 1966 Apr 11 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Grandma Pyle, Fortune Teller - revised script, 1965 Nov 18 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Grandpa Pyle's Good Luck Charm - revised script, 1964 Sep 21 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Writers: Allardice, James; Adair, Tom
  - Groom for Sergeant Carter's Sister (A) - revised script, 1965 Oct 4 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Grudge Fight (The) - script, no date (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Guest in the Barracks - revised script, 1964 Jun 8 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Home on the Range - revised script, 1965 Jul 19 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - How to Succeed in Farming Without Really Trying - revised script, 1966 Jul 27 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - It Takes Two to Tangle - revised script, 1966 Sep 9 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Jet Set (The) - revised script, 1965 Jan 18 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Just Move Your Lips, Sgt. - revised script, 1967 Aug 12 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Little Girl Blue - revised script, 1965 Dec 13 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Lost - The Colonel's Daughter - revised script, 1967 Jan 19 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Lou-Ann Poovie Sings Again - revised script, 1966 Dec 8 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Lou-Ann Poovie Sings No More - revised script, 1967 Feb 9 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Love Letters to the Sarge - revised script, 1964 Nov 9 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Love's Sweet Song - script, 1966 Aug 9 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Marry Me, Marry Me - revised script, 1966 Aug 17 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - My Buddy - War Hero - revised script, 1964 Dec 18 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Nobody Loves a Sergeant - revised script, 1964 Jul 21 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Officer Candidate Gomer Pyle - revised script, 1964 Nov 23 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Old Man Carter - revised script, 1964 Nov 24 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - One of Our Shells is Missing - script, 1967 Jan 30 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Opie Joins the Marines - revised script, 1966 Jan 27 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Pay Day - revised script, 1964 Jun 15 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - PFC Gomer Pyle - revised script, 1965 Jun 21 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Private Ralph Skunk - revised script, 1964 Jun 30 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Secret Life of Gomer Pyle (The) - revised script, 1966 Oct 11 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Sergeant Carter Dates a Pyle - revised script, 1965 Dec 6 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sergeant Carter, Marine Baby Sitter - revised script, 1964 Aug 19 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Sergeant Carter's Farewell to His Troops - revised script, 1964 Sep 30 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Sergeant of the Guard - revised script, 1965 Jan 25 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Sergeant of the Week - revised script, 1964 Sep 10 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Sgt Carter Gets a 'Dear John' Letter - revised script, 1964 Oct 23 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Show Me the Way to Go Home - revised script, 1966 Jul 14 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Showtime with Sergeant Carol - script, 1969 Feb 3 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Sing a Song of Papa - script, 1966 Dec 20 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Star is Born (A) - revised script, 1965 Dec 27 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Sue the Pants Off 'Em - script, 1966 Nov 17 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Supply Sergeants Never Die - revised script, 1965 Jul 26 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Survival of the Fattest - revised script, 1964 Jul 30 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - They Shall Not Pass - revised script, 1964 Aug 13 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Third Finger Left Loaf - revised script, 1965 Jul 28 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - To Re-Enlist of Not to Re-Enlist - revised script, 1966 Dec 1 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Vacation in Vegas - revised script, 1966 Jan 10 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Visit from Cousin Goober (A) - revised script, 1965 Sep 27 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Where There's A Will - revised script, 1967 Jan 12 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Writers: Markes, Larry
  - Whither the Weather? - revised script, 1966 Sep 28 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - You Bet Your Won Ton - script, 1966 Oct 25 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Good Morning World
  - 1st Down and 200 Miles to Go - revised script, 1967 Nov 17 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Writers: Vincent, E. Duke; Howard, Bruce
  - Brooks, Jim - revised script, 1967 Aug 1967 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Writers: Brooks, Jim
  - Don't Call Us and We Won't Call You - script, 1967 Jun 30 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Feet of Clay and a Head to Match - revised script, 1967 Aug 4 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Writers: Turteltaub, Saul; Orenstein, Bernie
  - For My Daughter's Hand You'll Get My Foot - revised script, 1967 Dec 6 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    Writers: Vincent, E. Duke; Johnson, Bruce
  - Here Comes the Bribe - revised script, 1967 Dec 15 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Writers: Howard, Bruce
  - Hutton's Mutt - revised script, 1967 Jan 5 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    Writers: Persky, Bill; Denoff, Sam; Vincent, E. Duke; Johnson, Bruce
  - I Love a Charade - revised script, 1967 Dec 4 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - I Want a Girl Just Like the Girl Who Married Dear Old Dave - revised script, 1967 Oct 6 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - If You Go Into the Blue Yonder, I'll Go Wild - revised script, 1967 Jun 23 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    Writers: Vincent, Edward Duke
  - If You Marry me Today, I'll Marry You Tomorrow - revised script, 1967 Sep 22 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Knits to You, Sir - script, 1967 Jun 16 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Lady and the Pussycat (The) - revised script, 1967 Dec 29 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Love at First Flight - revised script, 1967 Jul 5 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Man Who Came to Din-Din (The) - revised script, 1967 Oct 13 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - No News Like Nude News - revised script, 1967 Jul 28 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Now I Lay Me Down to Sleep, Maybe - revised script, 1967 Sep 8 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Writers: Vincent, E. Duke
  - Partner, Meet My Partner - revised script, 1967 Nov 10 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Return of Bibian (The) - revised script, 1967 Sep 1 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Writers: Orenstein, Bernie; Turteltaub, Saul
  - Voice of the Turtle is Better than Mine (The) - revised script, 1967 Sep 28 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Wedding Present (The) - revised script, 1967 Nov 3 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Where Have You Been, Billy Boy, Billy Boy - revised script, 1967 Aug 11 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Who Will Buy My Calamari? - script, 1967 Mar 14 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - You Can't Say That About My Wife…And, Neither Can I - revised script, 1967 Mar 21 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    Writers: Elliott, Peggy; Scharlach, Ed
  - You vs. Me - revised script, 1967 Jul 21 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Guns of Will Sonnett (The)
  - And a Killing Rode Into Town - script, 1967 Sep 13 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Writers: Dales, Arthur
  - And He Shall Lead the Children - script, 1967 Oct 25 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    Writers: Lakso, Edward J.
  - Bell for Jeff Sonnett (A) - revised script, 1967 Jun 5 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    Writers: Gould, Cliff
  - End of the Rope - script, 1967 Nov 16 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    Writers: Carr, Dick
  - Favor (The) - script, 1967 Jul 24 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Find a Sonnett, Kill a Sonnett - script, 1967 Oct 6 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Writers: Gordon, Larry
  - First Love - script, 1967 Sep 16 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Fool and his Money (A) - script, 1967 Dec 7 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    Writers: Pirosh, Robert
  - Grave for James Sonnet (A) - revised script, 1967 Mar 8 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Hero (The) - script, 1967 Sep 22 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Look for the Hound Dog - script, 1967 Oct 30 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Writers: Komack, James
  - Meeting at Devil's Fork - script, 1967 Jun 16 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Writers: Ware, Clyde
  - Message at Noon - script, 1967 Apr 27 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Natural Wax (The) - script, no date (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Of Lasting Summers and Jim Sonnett - script, no date (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Secret of Hangtown Mine - script, 1967 Aug 10 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Writers: Barrett, Tony
  - Sins of the Father (The) - script, 1967 Nov 27 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    Writers: Hite, Kathleen
  - Sunday in Paradise - script, 1967 Sep (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Turkey Shoot (The) - script, 1967 Jun 16 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Writers: Todd, Cliff
  - What's In a Name? - script, 1967 Oct 24 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- I Spy
  - A Room with a Rack - script, 1966 Jul 18 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    Writers: Zagor, Michael
  - Affair at T'sien Cha - revised script, 1964 Oct 6 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    Writers: Fine, Morton; Friedkin, David
  - Always Say Goodbye - script, 1965 Apr 7 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Always Say Goodbye - script, 1965 Apr 7 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - American [Empress] (An) - script, 1967 Jun 26 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    Writers: Moll, Elick; Than, Joseph
  - Anyplace I Hang Myself is Home - script, 1967 Jul 6 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Apollo - script, 1967 Aug 3 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Writers: Frankel, Ernest
  - Barter (The) - script (2 copies), 1965 May 11 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Beautiful Children (The) - script, 1967 Jan 16 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    Writers: Mather, Berkely
  - Bet Me a Dollar - script, 1965 Sep 25 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Blackout - script, [1966 Aug 8] (Box 37, Folder 13)
    Writers: Oringer, Barry
  - Bridge of Spies (The) - script, 1966 Apr 13 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Writers: Kandel, Stephen
  - Carry Me Back to the Old Tsing Tao - script, 1965 Mar 8 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Writers: Karp, David
  - Casanova Canarsie - script, 1966 Sep 22 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Child Out of Time - revised script, 1966 Sep 4 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Writers: Fine, Mort; Friedkin, David
  - Choice, The - script, 1967 Jun 7 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Chrysanthemum - revised script, 1965 Jun 2 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Conquest of Maude Murdock (The) - script, 1965 Oct 21 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Cops and Robbers - script, 1966 Dec 7 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    Writers: Ludwig, Jerry
  - Court of the Light - revised script, 1965 Dec 22 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    Writers: Culp, Robert
  - Court of the Lion - script, 1965 Jun 1 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Crusade to Limbo - revised script, 1966 Feb 2 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Writers: Friedkin, David; Fine, Mort
  - Cup of Kindness (A) - script, 1965 Jan 20 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Danny Was a Million Laughs - revised script, 1965 May 17 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Day Called 4 Jaguar (A) - script, 1965 Oct 22 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Dragon's Teeth - script, 1965 Feb 8 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    Writers: Ralston, Gilbert
  - Enchanted Cottage (The) - script, 1966 Aug 10 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Father Abraham - script, 1966 Apr 19 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Few Miles West of Nowhere (A) - script, 1967 Mar 21 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Get Thee to a Nunnery - script, 1966 Aug 15 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    Writers: Hargrove, Marion; Friedkin, David
  - Gift from Alexander (A), 1966 Mar 28 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Happy Birthday…Everybody - script, 1967 Jun 12 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Home to Judgment - script, 1967 Jul 12 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Honorable Assassins (The) - script, 1967 Jan 6 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    Writers: Pine, Les; Pine, Tina
  - It's All Done With Mirrors - revised script, 1965 Nov 9 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Laya - script, 1967 Feb 2 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Lisa (Bride By Mail) - script, 1966 Feb 25 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    Writers: Gillis, Jackson
  - Little Boy Lost - script, 1966 Feb 11 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    Writers: Krumholz, Chester
  - Lori - script, 1966 Feb 7 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Writers: Fine, Morton; Friedkin, Daivd
  - Loser (The) - revised script, 1965 Jun 22 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Lotus Eater (The) - script, 1967 Feb 2 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Medarra Block (The) - script, 1967 Feb 1 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Meek Shall Inherit the Chicks (The) - annotated script, 1966 Sep 12 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - My Mother, the Spy - script, 1965 Dec 23 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Name of the Game (The) - script, 1967 Jul 7 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Night Train to Madrid - script, 1966 Nov 15 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - No Exchange on Damaged Merchandise - script, 1965 Jan 12 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Now You See Her, Now You Don't - script, 1967 Feb 28 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Oedipus at Colonus - script, 1967 Feb 6 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    Writers: Hargrove, Marion
  - One of Our Bombs is Missing - script, 1966 Apr 18 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - One Thousand Fine - revised script, 1965 Nov 12 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    Writers: Graham, Colin
  - Philotino - script, 1966 Jan 23 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Pinwheel - script, 1967 Jul 7 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Plains in Spain (The) - script, 1966 Aug 15 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Red Sash of Courage - script, 1967 Feb 27 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    Writers: Crawford, Oliver
  - Return to Glory - script, 1965 Oct 18 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Rome…Take Away Three - script, 1966 Sep 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Seventh Captain (The) - script, 1967 Feb 7 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Shana - script, 1967 Jul 5 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - So Coldly Sweet - script, 1965 Jan 28 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - So Long, Patrick Henry - revised script, 1965 Mar 9 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Sophia - script, 1966 Apr 13 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Sparrowhawk (The) - revised script, 1966 Mar 7 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Tag, You're It - script, 1967 Jul 14 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Tatia - script, 1965 Jun 9 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    Writers: Lewin, Robert
  - There Was a Little Girl - revised script, 1966 Feb 16 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - There Was a Little Girl - revised script, 1966 Feb 8 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - This Guy Smith - script, 1967 Mar 20 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Three Hours on a Sunday Night - script, 1965 May 10 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Tiger (The) - script, 1965 May 4 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Tigers of Heaven - revised script, 1965 Sep 27 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Time of the Knife (The) - script, 1965 May 27 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - To Florence with Love (Part I) - script, 1966 Mar 22 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    Writers: Borisoff, Norman
  - To Florence with Love (Part II) - script, 1966 Mar 31 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Tonia - script, 1966 Apr 16 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Trial by Treehouse - script, 1966 Feb 25 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Trouble with Temple (The) - revised script, 1966 Sep 1 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Turkish Delight - revised script, 1965 Dec 28 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    Writers: Bercovici, Eric
  - Vendetta - script, 1966 Apr 21 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Warlord (The) - script, 1966 Mar 14 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Weight of the World - script, 1965 May 6 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Will the Real Good Guys Please Stand Up - script, 1966 Feb 14 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - You Can't Shoot an Honest Man - script, 1967 Feb 28 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Joey Bishop Show (The)
  - Andy Williams Visits Joey - script, 1964 Feb 11 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    Writers: Singer, Ray; Singer, Ray
  - Baby Formula (The) - revised script, 1963 Jan 21 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Baby Formula (The) - script, 1963 Jan 10 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Baby Nurse (The) - script, 1963 Mar 8 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Baby Sitter (The) - revised script, 1963 Aug 6 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Writers: Crane, Harry; Chambers, Ernest
  - Baby Sitter (The) - script, 1963 Aug 1 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Baby, It's Cold Inside - script, 1962 Aug 27 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Writers: Crane, Harry; Dreben, Stan
  - Baby's First Christmas (The) - script, 1963 Sep 30 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Baby's First Christmas (The) - script, 1963 Sep 20 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Baby's First Day (The) - script, no date (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Writers: Crane, Harry; Tackaberry, John
  - Bobby Rydell Stays at Joey's House - revised script, 1963 Oct 28 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Bobby Rydell Stays at Joey's House - script, 1963 Oct 2 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Breakup (The) - script, 1962 Jul 10 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Chance of a Lifetime - revised script, 1962 Oct 15 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Danny Give Joey Advice - revised script, 1963 Jun 4 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Formerly titled Joey and Danny Thomas
    Writers: Elinson, Iz; Fox, Fred S.
  - Deep in the Heart of Texas - script, 1962 Oct 1 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Double Play From Foster to Durocher to Joey - script, 1963 Nov 20 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Double Play From Foster to Durocher to Joey - script, 1963 Dec 2 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Double Time - revised script, 1962 Nov 5 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Writers: Dreben, Stan; Goodman, Ralph
  - Ellie Give Joey First Aid (Or: You Fracture Me) - script, 1963 May 16 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Ellie Gives Joey First Aid - revised script, 1963 Sep 13 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Ellie Gives Joey First Aid - script, 1963 Sep 9 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Ellie Goes to Court - script, 1964 Oct 12 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Ellie, the Talent Scout - script, 1962 Nov 29 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Every Dog Should Have a Boy - script, 1964 Jan 28 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Expectant Fathers' School (The) - script, 1963 Mar 3 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Writers: Marshall, Garry; Freeman, Fred
  - Fashion Show (The) - script, 1963 Aug 8 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Writers: Crane, Harry; Dreben, Harry
  - Freddy Goes High-Brow - revised script, 1962 Nov 26 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Hilda Quits - script, 1964 Jan 27 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Hilda Quits - script, 1964 Jan 15 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Hobby for Ellie (A) - script, 1964 Oct 29 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Honeymoon (The) - script, 1962 Jun 28 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Honeymoon is Over (The) - script, 1962 Sep 26 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Writers: [Fox, Fred S.]; [Elinson, Iz]
  - Hooray for Hollywood - script, 1962 Nov 1962 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - In This Corner, Jan Murray - revised script, 1964 Aug 31 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    Writers: Conway, Dick; MacLane, Roland
  - Jillson and the Cimmaron Buns - script, 1962 Nov 5 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Joey and Buddy Hackett Have a Luau - script, 1964 Jan 19 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Joey and Buddy Hackett Have a Luau - script, 1964 Jan (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Joey and Larry Split - script, 1964 Aug 5 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Writers: Phillips, Arthur
  - Joey and Milton and Baby Makes Three - revised script, 1963 Jun 20 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Formerly titled The Baby's Homecoming
  - Joey and Roberta Sherwood Play a Benefit - script, 1964 Jan 14 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Joey and Roberta Sherwood Play a Benefit - script, 1964 Jan 13 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Joey and the Laundry Bags - script, 1963 Jun 25 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Joey and the Los Angeles Dodgers - script, 1964 Feb 7 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Joey and the Los Angeles Dodgers - script, 1964 Feb 10 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Joey Changes Larry's Luck - revised script, 1965 Jan 21 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    Writers: Belson, Jerry
  - Joey Gets Brainwashed - script, 1963 Sep 6 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    Writers: Simon, Danny; Diamond, Mel; Rosen, Milt
  - Joey Gets Brainwashed (or Joey and Vic Demone) - script, 1963 Oct 7 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    Writers: Simon, Danny; Rosen, Milt; Diamond, Mel
  - Joey Goes to a Poker Party - revised script, 1964 Sep 24 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Joey Goes to CBS - revised script, 1964 Jul13 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Joey Insults Jack E. Leonard - script, 1963 Dec 16 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Joey Introduces Shecky Greene - script, 1964 Feb 25 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Joey Introduces Shecky Greene - script, 1964 Feb (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Joey is Invited to Washington - script, no date (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Joey is Invited to Washington - script, 1963 Nov 11 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Joey Junior's T.V. Debut - script, 1963 Jul 1 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Joey Leaves Ellie - script, 1962 Dec 3 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Joey Meets Edgar Bergen - script, 1963 Aug 13 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Joey Plugs the Laundry - revised script, 1963 Jul 29 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Joey Proposes to Ellie - script, 1963 Oct 21 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    Writers: Crane, Harry; Marshall, Garry
  - Joey Proposes to Ellie - script, 1963 Oct 10 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Joey Takes His Physical - script, 1963 Aug 24 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Joey the Comedian VS Larry the Writer - script, 1964 Jan 6 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Joey the Patient - revised script, 1964 Jul 28 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Writers: Morrow, Douglas
  - Joey VS. Oscar Levant - revised script, 1964 Aug 19 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Joey, Jack Jones and the Genie - script, 1964 Feb 17 (Box 22, Folder 2)